That's it, Annie!
I'd expect no less from my daughter!
What are you doing, Annie? No resting!
You mean you haven't heard?
WALL SINA
EAST WALL CITY
The Titan boy
and the big shots in charge of him
are apparently being called
to the capital.
And they're passing through
this city today.
I see.
Sounds like he'll be interrogated
for sure this time.
Whatever the case, I just hope
he passes through without a hitch
and has the gate shut firmly behind him.
Did you just mention sealing the gate?
You would suggest that
we defile the Walls even further?
Maria! Rose! Sina!
To defile the three goddesses is to
commit an unpardonable transgression!
-They love and worship the Walls as gods.
-Similar to gods,
-the Walls are impenetrable!
-Don't get involved.
-Man. They're still around?
-One shall worship, praise,
-Damn.
-and respect the Walls!
Our only protectors are the Walls!
STOHESS DISTRICT
MILITARY POLICE REGIMENT BRANCH OFFICE
You're finally up.
You look totally scary when you're asleep
that I couldn't wake you up.
Sorry, Annie.
You've been slacking a lot lately.
What's this? Are you mad already?
She's antisocial, all right.
Just leave her be.
She came here from Trost.
She's the only one here
who's seen real action.
It will take time for her to recuperate.
She's just been through hell.
I get it.
You have a thing for her.
What can you possibly like
about this girl?
Hitch.
There's only one way a ditz like you could
get into the Military Police Regiment.
Whatever do you mean by that?
-Say it to my face.
-Enough, you two!
Oh, take it easy, guys.
I have actual work for you today
instead of the usual odd jobs.
That's why I called you here.
It's about the Scout Regiment group
being summoned to the capital.
They're passing through
this town's main street today.
The Military Police Regiment HQ will be
serving as their security escorts,
so we only need to assist
while they pass through.
Omnidirectional mobility within
city limits is temporarily authorized.
You'll follow beside
the convoy and help bolster security.
You'll also head to
the starting point by barge.
That is all.
May I ask something, sir?
What is it?
What are we supposed to protect
the convoy from?
I've never heard of anyone inside
this Wall defying the Royal Government.
There may be petty criminals,
but I can't imagine
actual organizations trying anything
unless they're based outside the Wall.
I'm not even sure what motive they'd have.
Oh, you're a serious one!
You're in charge now.
The details are all in here.
What?
We officers are busy enough as it is.
Prove that you can handle this yourselves.
But no screw-ups. Got it?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Shall we continue?
Whose turn is it again?
Damn! This is messed up!
Yes, this organization is
way more rotten than I had imagined.
Well, that is why I chose it,
but you get stuck doing all the work
when you're a rookie here.
Man, why didn't anyone tell me?
Bastard.
All he can think about is himself!
What are you talking about, Marlo?
Choosing to join
the Military Police Regiment
makes you no different from him.
No. I'm nothing like you degenerates.
I came here to fix
the Military Police Regiment!
Wow, Marlo!
I never took you for that sort of guy!
How are you going to fix it?
By getting to the top, of course.
Once I'm at the top, I'll amend the rules
and make the corrupt pay fairly
for their injustices.
It's that simple!
I'll simply turn them back
into normal people. That's all.
Back into the people
they're supposed to be.
Oh, man! You're the real deal!
Sorry! I originally took you
for a stick-in-the-mud!
That's quite a noble goal.
Good luck with that.
I wonder.
If a do-gooder like you took charge,
I think that would spell the end for us.
Oh, so you can talk?
I think you're an honest person
because you say honest things.
I know there are people like that.
It takes a lot of courage
to go against the flow.
I respect that.
It could just be that
you're all fools though.
No, maybe they are,
but don't lump me in with them!
Enough of this chit-chat. Let's go!
The escort wagons will pass through
the outer gate in forty-five minutes.
When we get there, find your positions.
-Understood?
-Yes.
Hey, now!
What's that?
That's our equipment!
They must be taking it to the interior.
Still, it's strange for
the merchant association to be involved.
What are they...
They're illegally selling
government-issued equipment?
Hey, now! What about our assignment?
Oh, man! He's the real deal!
Well, for better or worse,
we do have time.
This will make for
some nice entertainment.
So how about a drink?
Yes? What do you want, rookie?
It's against the law
to sell government property.
So?
Government property is paid for
by the citizens' hard-earned tax money.
Therefore...
Wow, a rookie blackmailing
his superior officers.
You've got a bright future in store.
Go get yourself a girl
or something and refresh yourself.
What?
Wait!
It's against the law to sell...
Hey!
You're under arrest for
a treasonable offense against a superior.
Don't be stupid.
Such disrespect for the law--
...is perfectly acceptable.
Here, anyway!
I think that's enough.
Don't you think so too?
So sorry about that!
It seems our idiot has caused you trouble.
We'll teach him a lesson, don't worry.
Or...
would you prefer to have
an even bigger problem on your hands?
Just this once.
-Yes, sir!
-Now, let's get that drink.
-Yes. I'd say we earned it.
Go on.
You're going to make the dishonest
pay for their injustices, right?
I'm not against helping you out with that.
Damn it!
You're certainly a hard worker, missy.
Oh, no, you're too kind.
Those people you know...
Those fools you mentioned earlier...
Would they have done it?
They might have.
You mentioned going against the flow.
I guess I'm just another piece
of scum being swept away by it.
I don't know.
But maybe that's just
the way ordinary people are?
Personally,
even if it means being
a weakling swept up in the flow,
being seen as a person is all I want.
Annie.
Hi.
Looks like you're
a full-fledged Military Police now.
Armin.
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm a cargo carrier.
I'm hiding omnidirectional mobility
equipment under this rain gear.
See?
What is this about?
Annie.
Could you help us let Eren escape?
Escape to where?
Defying the government's orders...
Where could he run to inside these Walls?
We just need to hide him for a while.
We won't be explicitly rebelling
against the government.
It will basically be an act of defiance
by part of the Scout Regiment.
We're going to buy enough time
to gather some things
that will unquestionably overturn
the council's say in the matter.
Overturn it?
There's really something that handy?
How are you so sure?
I'm sorry. I can't say.
Sorry, but I can't accept.
I won't tell anyone though. Good luck.
Annie!
Please!
They're going to kill Eren!
A bunch of people who know nothing
are unwittingly pushing humanity
toward the brink of self-extinction
simply to save their own necks!
I realize it sounds less than convincing.
But even so, we have no choice
but to bet everything now!
Of course, we'll try hard
not to cause you trouble,
but we absolutely need
the Military Police Regiment's help
to sneak him through
Wall Sina's security checkpoint.
This is our only option left.
Tell me.
Do I look like that good
of a person to you?
A good person...
Actually,
I've never been fond
of phrasing it that way.
Because to me,
it feels like it's only used
to refer to people you use
for your own convenience.
And I don't think there's anyone
who's convenient to everyone.
Which is why, if you do say no to this,
that would make you
a bad person in my eyes.
Okay.
I'll do it.
We got through surprisingly easily.
That's the mighty
Military Police Regiment for you.
It goes to show what kind of work they do.
Don't look around at everything.
Let's just hope they haven't realized
Jean took my place.
That definitely won't last for long.
He and I look nothing alike.
It will be fine.
You both have the same
sort of mean, nasty look to you.
I don't have his horseface!
Say,
how were you planning to get over the Wall
if I hadn't agreed to help?
We were going to barge through
using omnidirectional mobility gear.
That's crazy.
Couldn't you have just escaped
before reaching Stohess
to avoid all this trouble
in the first place?
Why did it have to be here and now?
I thought this town's complex layout
would make our body double ploy
more likely to succeed.
Plus, acting dutifully
and keeping their defenses down
will buy us far more time to escape
than head-on opposition would.
I see. Good point.
Over there!
Here?
Yes. We're going through here.
It's what's left of an underground city
they were planning to make.
It leads to the vicinity
of the outer gate.
Really? That's amazing.
Annie?
Oh, man.
Don't tell me you're afraid of dark,
cramped places or something.
Yes. I am.
I doubt a brave, suicidal maniac like you
would understand
how a delicate damsel feels.
Any damsel who can flip a grown man
upside down isn't weak at all.
Cut the crap! Let's hurry!
No. I'm not going.
I'm afraid to go down there.
I'm not helping
unless we stay above ground.
Quit being stupid! Just get down here!
Stop screwing around!
Eren! Don't shout!
I'm sure it's fine, Mikasa.
Because for some reason, this whole area
has been completely deserted for a while.
Man. That really hurts.
At what point did you
start looking at me that way,
Armin?
Annie.
Why did you have
Marco's omnidirectional mobility gear?
It had all the same scrapes and bumps.
I could tell because I had helped him
do maintenance on it.
Yes.
I found it and took it.
Then those two Titans we captured alive,
was it you who killed them?
Who knows?
But if that's what you had suspected
a month ago,
why didn't you do anything then?
Even now, I can hardly believe it.
I just wanted to believe
I had it all wrong.
That's why I didn't.
Still, back then...
The fact that you didn't kill me back then
is why we're in this situation now.
Yes, I agree with all my heart.
I never imagined
you'd end up cornering me like this.
Why didn't I do anything then?
Hold on, Annie!
There's still a chance
you're going along with all this
as part of some horrible, idiotic joke!
Just get down here!
There's something you can prove
just by coming down here!
Come down here and prove it!
I can't go down there.
I'm a failed warrior.
I'm being serious here! This isn't funny!
Talk to us, Annie!
We can still discuss this as--
Enough.
I can't listen to any more of this.
It's pointless.
I'm going to carve you up again,
Female Titan!
Armin.
It's nice that I could be
a "good person" for you.
For now, you've won your bet.
But
my bet
begins now!
Eren!
Mikasa?
It's too late.
The Female Titan was actually
Annie Leonhart all along.
However, even when faced with her,
Eren is unable to transform.
Because she's Annie.